# Md. Towhidul Islam Piyas

#### Marketing Executive

I am a talented, ambitious and hardworking individual, with broad skills and experience in digital and printed marketing, social media and leading projects. Furthermore, I am adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well under pressure.





towhidulislampiyas999@gmail.com



473 North Shahjahanpur, Dhaka-1217, Dhaka, Bangladesh



in linkedin.com/in/md-towhidul-islam-piyas-4325a3194

+880 1950095915



07 December, 1996

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Business Administration**

City University

04/2017 - 05/2021

CGPA - 3.18 out of 4.00

Courses

Maior - Marketing

Minor - HRM

# **Higher School Certificate**

Notre Dame College

2014 - 2016

GPA - 4.75 out of 5.00

Group - Science

# **Secondary School Certificate**

Motijheel Govt. Boys' High School

GPA - 5.00 out of 5.00

Courses

Group - Science

### **Junior School Certificate**

Motijheel Govt. Boys' High School

2011 - 2011

GPA - 5.00 out of 5.00

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Marketing Executive**

The Golden Fibre Trade Centre Ltd.

109 (5th floor), Masjid Road, Old DOHS, Banani, Dhaka-1206, Bangladesh

The Golden Fibre Trade Centre Ltd. is a Jute & Jute Goods trading and exporting company.

#### **Chief Editor & Brand Promoter**

#### **Hungry Panda Bangladesh**

12/2019 - 08/2021

Zia Soroni Road, Polashpur, Donia, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Online homemade food delivery company.

# **Customer Service & Operations**

Genex Infoysis (Uber Process) 11/2019 - 03/2020

Nikunja 2, Khilkhet, Dhaka-1229, Bangladesh

A third party call center company of Uber.

#### **Telemarketer**

SkyTech Solutions Ltd.

06/2019 - 09/2019

House No 1, Road 10/A, Sector 9, Uttara Model Town, Dhaka-1230, Bangladesh

IT firm as well as outbound call center company.

#### **SKILLS**



# **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Ex 'Cultural Secretary' of 'Notre Dame Natya Dal' (NDND).

I used to do music shows when I was in college.

I was the "Cadet Under Officer" (CUO) at "Bangladesh National Cadet Corps" (BNCC).

I was "Young Leader" of "British Council" club in school.

I participated at "ICC World Cup" from cultural club of school to represent Bangladesh in 2011.

I participated at "South Asian Games" from cultural club of school to represent Bangladesh in 2010.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Bengali

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

# INTERESTS

